{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Tina gave me _____ book for my birthday.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- a (n) + countable nouns\n- we use \"a\" before words that begin with consonants",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I read ____ book Tina gave me while I was on holiday.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- the book Tina gave me (it is clear in the situation)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sally lives in _____ big house in the country.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- a (n) + countable nouns\n- we use \"a\" before words that begin with consonants",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Brian's house is over there. It's _____ big one with lots of plants in the front garden.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- the big one with lots of plants (It is clear in the situation)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Excuse me. Is there _____ Post Office near here?",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- a (n) + countable nouns\n- we use \"a\" before words that begin with consonants",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you tell me where _____ nearest Post Office is, please?",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Remember: the + superlative form",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Christine and Gerald saw _____ horror film last night.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- a (n) + countable nouns\n- we use \"a\" before words that begin with consonants",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tina went to the cinema on Friday night. She enjoyed _____ film, but thought it was too long.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- the film (that Tina saw, it is clear in the situation)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have to go to _____ bank this afternoon to pay in a cheque.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Remember: go to the bank but go to school",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ben lives in Manchester but twice _____ week he has to work in London.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- We use: once, twice, etc ... + a week",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}